<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Patricia Horvath</title>
    <link>http://patricialhorvath.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Patricia Horvath</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2016 22:41:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://patricialhorvath.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Grants and Awards</title>
      <link>http://patricialhorvath.com/grants-and-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2016 22:41:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://patricialhorvath.com/grants-and-awards/</guid>
      <description> Notable Essay of 2015, Best American Essays, 2016 for &amp;ldquo;Wrath&amp;rdquo; (The Los Angeles Review) Literature Fellowship in Fiction, New York Foundation for the Arts, 2015 Special Mention, Pushcart Prize XXXVII, Best of the Small Presses, 2013 Goldenberg Prize in Fiction, Bellevue Literary Review, 2011 Residency Fellowship, Can Serrat International Artists’ Center, El Bruc, Spain, 2010 Literature Fellowship in Creative Nonfiction, New York Foundation for the Arts, 2007 Residency Fellowship, Blue Mountain Center for the Creative Arts, Blue Mountain Lake, NY 2007 New York Times Foundation Fellowship, 2006 Residency Fellowship, Millay Colony for the Arts, Austerlitz, NY, 2006 Barbara Deming Memorial Fund, New York, NY, 2005 Residency Fellowship, Hedgebrook Foundation, Whidbey Island, WA, 2005  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>http://patricialhorvath.com/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2014 18:15:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://patricialhorvath.com/teaching/</guid>
      <description>I teach creative writing and literature at Framingham State University, Massachusetts. One of my courses, Disability in Literature and Culture, considers the ways in which disabled bodies are represented in literary texts. My interest in this subject stems from my experience with scoliosis and my curiosity about the relationship between disability and self-identity. It&amp;#8217;s a topic I explore in my forthcoming memoir, All the Difference (Etruscan Press).
I&amp;#8217;ve given readings and presentations at The New York Public Library, Fashion Institute of Technology, SUNY Purchase, The Millay Colony for the Arts, The Hurston-Wright Foundation Conference at Virginia Commonwealth University, the Association of Writing and Writing Programs annual conference, and Bellevue Literary Review&amp;#8217;s annual reading at Bellevue Hospital, Langone Medical Center in New York, among other venues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>http://patricialhorvath.com/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2014 18:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://patricialhorvath.com/publications/</guid>
      <description>Stories  “Luck Was a Taxi” Confrontation, Issue No. 118, Fall 2015 “Poinsettias” (short fiction) The Saranac Review, Issue 9, Fall 2013 “Sea Change” Confrontation, Issue No. 113, Spring 2013 “Sunrise” Confrontation, Issue No. 113, Spring 2013 Reprinted in Route Nine: Route9 “Never Let Go” Georgetown Review, Vol. 14, No. 1, Spring 2013 “Hold on Fast” The Laurel Review, Vol. 46, No. 1, Spring 2012 “But Now Am Found” The Bellevue Literary Review, Vol.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://patricialhorvath.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2014 14:40:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://patricialhorvath.com/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://patricialhorvath.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2014 01:09:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://patricialhorvath.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Patricia Horvath&amp;rsquo;s essays and stories have appeared in numerous literary journals, including The Massachusetts Review, The Los Angeles Review, New Ohio Review, Shenandoah, Confrontation, The Laurel Review, 2 Bridges Review, and Cream City Review. She is the recipient of the Bellevue Literary Review&amp;rsquo;s Goldenberg Prize in Fiction for a story that was accorded a Special Mention in the 2013 Pushcart Prize anthology and of a Notable Essay designation in the 2016 edition of Best Americae Essays.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>