<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Patricia Horvath</title>
    <link>http://patricialhorvath.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Patricia Horvath</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2016 22:41:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://patricialhorvath.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Grants and Awards</title>
      <link>http://patricialhorvath.com/grants-and-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2016 22:41:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://patricialhorvath.com/grants-and-awards/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Literature Fellowship in Fiction, New York Foundation for the Arts, 2015&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Special Mention, Pushcart Prize XXXVII, Best of the Small Presses, 2013&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Goldenberg Prize in Fiction, Bellevue Literary Review, 2011&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Residency Fellowship, Can Serrat International Artists’ Center, El Bruc, Spain, 2010&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Literature Fellowship in Creative Nonfiction, New York Foundation for the Arts, 2007&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Residency Fellowship, Blue Mountain Center for the Creative Arts, Blue Mountain Lake, NY 2007&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New York Times Foundation Fellowship, 2006&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Residency Fellowship, Millay Colony for the Arts, Austerlitz, NY, 2006&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Barbara Deming Memorial Fund, New York, NY, 2005&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Residency Fellowship, Hedgebrook Foundation, Whidbey Island, WA, 2005&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>http://patricialhorvath.com/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2014 18:15:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://patricialhorvath.com/teaching/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I teach creative writing and literature at Framingham State University, Massachusetts. One of my courses, Disability in Literature and Culture, considers the ways in which disabled bodies are represented in literary texts. My interest in this subject stems from my experience with scoliosis and my curiosity about the relationship between disability and self-identity. It&amp;#8217;s a topic I explore in my forthcoming memoir, &lt;em&gt;All the Difference&lt;/em&gt; (Etruscan Press).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#8217;ve given readings and presentations at The New York Public Library, Fashion Institute of Technology, SUNY Purchase, The Millay Colony for the Arts, The Hurston-Wright Foundation Conference at Virginia Commonwealth University, the Association of Writing and Writing Programs annual conference, and Bellevue Literary Review&amp;#8217;s annual reading at Bellevue Hospital, Langone Medical Center in New York, among other venues.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>http://patricialhorvath.com/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2014 18:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://patricialhorvath.com/publications/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;stories&#34;&gt;Stories&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;“Luck Was a Taxi” Confrontation, Issue No. 118, Fall 2015&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;“Poinsettias” (short fiction) The Saranac Review, Issue 9, Fall 2013&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;“Sea Change” Confrontation, Issue No. 113, Spring 2013&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://route9litmag.com/post/80855249568/sunrise&#34;&gt;“Sunrise” Confrontation, Issue No. 113, Spring 2013 &lt;br&gt;Reprinted in Route Nine: Route9&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;“Never Let Go” Georgetown Review, Vol. 14, No. 1, Spring 2013&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;“Hold on Fast” The Laurel Review, Vol. 46, No. 1, Spring 2012&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;“But Now Am Found” The Bellevue Literary Review, Vol. 11, No. 1, Spring 2011&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;“Vigil” Iron Horse Literary Review, Vol. 8, No. 2, Spring 2007&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;“Flesh” iris, Issue 52, Spring 2006&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;“Bonita” Puerto del Sol, Spring 2006&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;“Accident” 580 Split, Vol. 7, Spring 2005&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;“Wakey Nights” Shenandoah, Vol. 54, No. 2, Fall 2004&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;essays&#34;&gt;Essays&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;“Patience” The Massachusetts Review, Vol. LVI, No. 4, Winter 2015&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;“Wrath” The Los Angeles Review, Volume 18, Fall 2015&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;“Gluttony” Harpur Palate, Vol. 14, No. 2, Winter/Spring, 2015&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;“Envy” New Ohio Review, Issue 16, Fall 2014&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://issuu.com/2bridgesreview/docs/2bridgesreview2013/112?e=0/8209720&#34;&gt;“The Frozen Sea” 2 Bridges Review, City University of New York, Volume 3, Fall 2013&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.vidaweb.org/by-circumstance-and-design-gender-writing-and-interiority/&#34;&gt;“By Circumstance &amp;amp; Design: Gender, Writing and Interiority” Essay posted on the website for VIDA: Women in Literary Arts, May 2011&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;“Caged” Cream City Review, Vol. 32, No. 2, Fall 2008&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;reviews-interviews&#34;&gt;Reviews/Interviews&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://tetheredbyletters.com/author-qa-patricia-horvath/&#34;&gt;Tethered by Letters, Author Interview Series, May 17, 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.newpages.com/literary-magazine-reviews/2014-06-16/#2-Bridges-Review-V3-201&#34;&gt;New Pages, Review, “The Frozen Sea” June 16, 2014&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://blr.med.nyu.edu/content/interviews/2011-contest-winners/patti-horvath&#34;&gt;Author interview, Bellevue Literary Review Online&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://patricialhorvath.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2014 14:40:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://patricialhorvath.com/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://patricialhorvath.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2014 01:09:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://patricialhorvath.com/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;alignleft wp-image-47 size-medium&#34; src=&#34;http://patricialhorvath.com/images/Patti_Bio_pic-200x300.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; width=&#34;200&#34; height=&#34;300&#34; srcset=&#34;http://patricialhorvath.com/images/Patti_Bio_pic-200x300.jpg 200w, http://patricialhorvath.com/images/Patti_Bio_pic.jpg 300w&#34; sizes=&#34;(max-width: 200px) 100vw, 200px&#34; /&gt; Patricia Horvath&amp;rsquo;s essays and stories have appeared in numerous literary journals, including &lt;em&gt;The Massachusetts Review&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;The Los Angeles Review&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;New Ohio Review&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Shenandoah&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Confrontation&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;The Laurel Review&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;2 Bridges Review&lt;/em&gt;, and &lt;em&gt;Cream City Review&lt;/em&gt;. She is the recipient of the &lt;em&gt;Bellevue Literary Review&amp;rsquo;s&lt;/em&gt; Goldenberg Prize in Fiction for a story that was accorded a Special Mention in the 2013 Pushcart Prize anthology. Her memoir &lt;em&gt;All the Difference&lt;/em&gt; (Etruscan Press), for which she received fellowships from The New York Foundation for the Arts and the Barbara Deming Memorial Fund, explores the connection between disability and self-identity and what happens to one&amp;rsquo;s sense of self when a physical disability ceases to be visible. She teaches at Framingham State University, Massachusetts and is an editor at &lt;em&gt;The Massachusetts Review&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>